Aurel Jared C. Dantis

O Diliman, Quezon City, PH

∂ dantis.me/

jareddantis@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jareddantis

Profile

Computer science undergraduate with a passion for the visual arts and a desire to unite timely information with good design. Has experience creating websites, promotional materials, and other media for various purposes, ranging from personal projects to academic requirements and events.

Education

University of the Philippines Diliman

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science · 2019 — present

Philippine Science High School Main Campus

Secondary · 2013 — 2019

University of the Philippines Integrated School

Primary ⋅ 2006 — 2013

Skills

Web Development

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
CSS preprocessors (SCSS, Less, Stylus)
Vue.js 2 + Vuetify
PHP + MySQL
Bootstrap + jQuery

Programming

Python 3 (discord.py, Flask) C

Prototyping

Figma

Adobe Creative Cloud

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Lightroom Premiere Pro

Development Tools

Linux/Unix Bash scripting Git

Experience

Branding & Creatives Manager, CURSOR++

Sep 2021 - May 2022

Designed branding and digital media for the Academic Year 2021-2022 installment of CURSOR++, a series of internal workshops geared towards developing professional, technical, and soft skills of UP CURSOR members.

WebUpdates Team Head, UP CURSOR 2122A

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022

Designed the new UP CURSOR website for 2022 and led the team responsible for the website design and the online announcement materials for the UP Association of Computer Science Majors (UP CURSOR).

Info & PR Head, UP CURSOR 1920A Talents Night

Oct 2019

Led the information and public relations committee for the UP CURSOR Talents Night of Batch 1920A, in the creation of the batch branding, profile pictures, and event publicity materials.

Publicity Committee Member, BRAIN BLAST!

Dec 2018 - Jan 2019

Designed branding, print, and digital media for the annual PSHS-MC research fair, featuring research projects in different fields by select Grade 12 students.

Lead Graphic Designer, IMPETU Benefit Concert

Apr 2018

Designed branding, print, and digital media for the PSHS-MC EPTC's benefit concert.

Awards & citations

University Scholar

First & Second Semester AY 2020-2021, First Semester AY 2019-2020 University of the Philippines Diliman

Oblation Scholarship Awardee, 2019

University of the Philippines Diliman

Undergraduate Merit Scholarship Awardee, 2019

Science Education Institute, Department of Science and Technology

Director's Lister, Grades 7-12

Philippine Science High School Main Campus

Workshops & conferences attended

lskolart Nov 2018

Conference on the application of design in an educational context, and the state of art in current Philippine society.

PSHSS 2018 Science Research Summit

Sep - Oct 2018

Convention of PSHS scholars from all over the Philippines that aims to increase the community's knowledge and appreciation of Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM).

Graphika Manila 2018

Feb 2018

Annual conference on the current state of and trends in design, with talks from veterans of various fields in the industry.

TEDxYouth@PSHSMain

May 2017

Conference that aims to spark discussion and connection through talks given by experts from various fields, from mathematics to the arts.

Projects

Rico

https://github.com/jareddantis/rico-bot

A Discord bot written in Python 3 that helps servers keep track of songs, videos, and websites recommended to its members. Made with discord.py and deployed on Google Cloud Compute Engine.

send-e.ml https://send-e.ml

A web app that creates links that transform into fully-fledged e-mail templates. Great for support e-mails, petitions, and other correspondences that benefit from a standardized format. Written in vanilla HTML5 and deployed on GitHub Pages.

General Weighted Average (GWA) Calculator

https://calc.dantis.me

A web app that lets students quickly estimate their current class standing. Written in Vue.js 2, made with Vuetify, and deployed on Netlify.

Playman

https://playman.dantis.me

A web app for managing your Spotify playlists, even while on the go. Supports shuffling, merging, backups and more. Written in Vue.js 2, made with Vuetify, and deployed on Netlify.